



Davide Deluk

Graphic Designer & Snowboard Instructor

I am a graphic designer and snowboard instructor, I was born on February 17th 1986 and I have more than 10 years of experience in the communication industry. I am a courious, challenging and positive person, I like to share new pojects and ideas, I am always ready to face new experiences. Accuracy and responsibility are always present during my daily work, with the aim to reach the predetermined target. I love nature and sports, my passion are snowboarding, trekking and the ice cream.





🔍 +39 333 86 67 710 🔀 davide@davidedeluk.com 😘 davidedeluk.com





Professional Experience

January 2016 - Today

February 2014 - December 2015

May 2014 - December 2014

September 2013 - April 2014

November 2011 - August 2013

July 2009 - June 2011

September 2005 - July 2009

FREELANCE

Some clients

KORFF S.R.L. | GANASSINI CORPORATE | LA TUA PASTA | INTERFACE FACILITY MANAGEMENT S.R.L. | WILD ACADEMY

GANASSINI CORPORATE, MILANO

Art Director

FACTORY PRIME S.R.L., MILANO

Graphic Designer

LA TUA PASTA, LONDON

Sales Assistant

During this experience I improved English language, my organization ability and the capability to relate with public.

FACTORY PRIME S.R.L., MILANO

Graphic Designer

GAIA COMUNICAZIONE S.R.L., MILANO

Graphic Designer

MORE LIGHT, MILANO

Junior Graphic Designer



Education

September 2000 - June 2005

January 2006 - June 2006

July 2013 - August 2013

October 2013 - March 2014

April 2016 - April 2017

LICEO ARTISTICO CARAVAGGIO, MILANO

High School Diploma

IED, MILANO

Art Direction Master

ABEA S.R.L., MILANO

Web Design course

CALLAN SCHOOL, LONDON

English course

COLLEGIO MAESTRI DI SCI E SNOWBOARD, ITALY

Snowboard Instructor course



Capabilities











Interests & Hobby

















